# **Ana Bollain**

# **Front-end Developer**





### About me

Curious by nature, I define myself as persevering and resourceful. With great adaptability, my empathy, collaborative attitude and commitment make me a great team player.

Thanks to over 6 years of work experience in France and Spain, communicating in both english and french, I have mastered both project planning and stress management to meet client expectations with tight deadlines.

## Soft skills

Teamwork
Empathy
Problem Solving
Attention to detail
Creative Thinking
Responsiveness
Adaptability
Management

# **Proyectos**

Rick & Morty CD
Personal Project | React JS

Minion's Cards CD
Team Project | Javascript

Legacy JS Code Upgrading 
Team Project | React & Node JS

Adalabers 👄 Personal Project | React JS

Whack Tartalo 👄 Personal Project | Javascript

# **Experience**

#### Front-end Developer

Bootcamp Adalab | Remote | Sept. 2022 - Dec. 2022

- > Layout: HTML5, CSS3, Sass, Responsive Design, Flexbox, CSS Grid.
- > Javascript (ES6) and creation of a SPA application with React.
- > Developing a basic REST API with Node JS and Express JS.
- > SQLite for creating and managing databases and EJS Template Engine.
- > Version control with Git.
- > Project development under SCRUM framework and Agile philosophy.
- > Development tools: Gulp, Visual Studio Code, Terminal, Zeplin.
- > Communication skills and team work: Slack, Github, Railway.

#### Partner Architect & Freelance Interior Designer

Freelance. Remote | March 2022 - Oct. 2022 Estudi Biga SCCLP. Barcelona | Sept. 2019 - March 2022 Katty Schiebeck. Barcelona | April 2019 - Oct. 2019

- > Management and development of projects as a team leader.
- > Coordination of all parties involved for project decision-making.
- > Design, illustration and 3D rendering of creative proposals.
- > Production of techinal and administrative documentation.
- > Adaptabilty to tigtht deadlines with high quality standards.

#### **Architect & Interior Designer**

Atelier du Pont. Paris | Jan. 2017 - March 2019 AWP. Paris | March 2016 - Oct. 2016

- > Contact with clients in oral presentations and project follow-up.
- > Analysis of commercial proposals and compliance with client's budget.
- > Contact with sales representatives for the prescription of materials.
- > Management and development of residential and hospitality projects.

## Education

#### **Intensive Front-end Development Bootcamp**

Adalab | Remote | Sept. 2022 - Dec. 2022

#### **Online Web Development Courses**

Platzi | Remote | July 2022 - Sept. 2022 HTML5 & CSS3 | CSS Grid | Javascript | JS Engine (V8) & Browser

#### **Basics of Web Development & Coding**

Coursera. University of Michigan | Remote | April 2022 - June 2022

#### **Master of Architecture**

ETSAM. Polytechnic University of Madrid | Sept. 2008 - July 2015

#### **Architecture & Landscape Exchange Program**

KTH. Sweden | Erasmus | Sept. 2012 - July 2013

# Technical Skills Languages

$\odot$	HTML5	$\bigcirc$	Gulp	Spanish
$\bigcirc$	CSS3	$\bigcirc$	Git	Native
$\bigcirc$	Sass	$\bigcirc$	Agile	English
$\bigcirc$	Javascript	$\bigcirc$	Scrum	Professional. C1 Advanced (CAE)
$\odot$	React JS	$\bigcirc$	InDesign	French
$\odot$	Node JS	$\bigcirc$	Illustrator	Fluent
$\bigcirc$	SQLite	$\bigcirc$	Photoshop	Basque

Native, EGA